goodnightnaturals.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy is a serious concern. Information is not shared and private.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Paul at [cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com](mailto:cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com)

**What this policy covers**  
This policy covers how Good Night Naturals treats personal information that we receive, including information related to your past use of our services, as well as non-personalized information collected from our Web site [www.goodnightnaturals.com](http://www.goodnightnaturals.com/) Personal information is information about you, which is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, phone number, etc.

**Our Commitment To Your Privacy**  
We respect our customers right to privacy. No Information given to us on this web site will be given out or sold, and will only be used for internal business purposes. All personal information, such as your name, postal, email address, payment information (i.e. credit card information etc), is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information which you provide is stored in a secure location, and accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provided the information (such as to process your order, reply to an email or brochure request, etc). In addition, all online orders (credit card info, etc) are additionally protected by being encrypted). 

Personal information will NOT be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provided the information, such as processing of credit card charges, or released, unless required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we provide or sell personal information to third parties 

Our web site ([http//www.goodnightnaturals.com](http://www.goodnightnaturals.com/)) utilizes cookies to manage our shopping cart for the purpose of processing orders. Cookies are also set by third parties in order to track our network ads performance. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not the names, address or other information about our visitors that would identify the particular visitors to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by Good Night Naturals and staff. 

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. 

Furthermore, our web site tracks information about the visits to our web site. For example, we compile statistics to show the daily number of visitors to our site, the daily requests for particular files, what countries those request came from, etc. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, however, these statistics contain NO personal information and cannot be used to gather such information 

**The Information We Collect**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our web site (http//www.earthske.com) On some pages you can order products, make brochure requests, or ask a question about or products or services. The types of information collected on these pages include:

**Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone Number  
Credit Card Information  
Billing address  
Shipping name and address**

**The Ways we Use Information**  
Good Night Naturals does not sell, rent, or share personal information about you, our customer, with other people or nonaffiliated organizations.

We use the information provided by you when placing an order only to complete that order, or to fulfill your request for more information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order, or as required by the law. This includes your personal information, or information provided about someone else. We use your return email address to answer the email we receive. If you request to be added to our store newsletter, or wish to receive special offers from us, your email address will be used in sending out this information. Please refer to the Choice/Opt out section below for removal from our newsletter and promotional emails. At any time you may ask to be removed from our newsletter or ask us to stop sending special offers. Such addresses are used only for these purposes and are not shared with any outside parties.

Finally, we never use or share personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**  
In order to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain. Simply email [cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com](mailto:cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com), or call 415.738.8379. Leave your name and number so we can call you back to verify your identity and change your personally identifiable information.

For our customers security we do NOT allow online orders that were placed to be changed by adding or deleting items from it after an order has been placed (of course before you place your order you can modify or change the contents of your shopping cart). You may however correct spelling mistakes. See below. In order to add or delete items you will need to cancel the order within 24 hours after being placed on line and create a new order. After that your order will be processed.

SEE BELOW ON HOW TO CORRECT SPELLING MISTAKES. See our Online Billing Policy. Within 24 hours after your order is placed (unless you requested rush service), you may cancel it if you have made a spelling mistake. Simply email [cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com](mailto:cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com) or call 415.738.8379, and leave your order number and the fact you want to cancel your order, or tell us what spelling changes need to be made. If you call us and leave a message, please make sure you leave your phone number for verification. We will not change any information without a way in which to reach you. We will let you know when you order has been cancelled. If you don't know your order number and want to cancel it, you must provide us with your name and a phone number we can reach you. You may call us at the above phone number or email us. We will then call you and ask some personal information about your order to verify and correct it. At that point we will delete your order and you may then enter a new one if you wish.

In order to protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to ascertain your identity before granting access and making corrections.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

CHOICE/OPT-OUT: Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional e-mails or newsletter may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending an email with the message "remove from email list" in the subject line, indicating that you no longer wish to receive promotional emails from us.

**How to Contact Us**  
If there are any questions or concerns in regards to these privacy policies, we may be reached at:  
**Mailing Address**  
Good Night Naturals  
1418 W Poinsettia Pl Ste. 8  
West Hollywood, CA 90046  
Phone: 415.738.8379  
email: [cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com](mailto:cust_serv@goodnightnaturals.com)

_Privacy policy effective 11/1/2006_
